

I am an energetic and hardworking individual with a strong ability to multi-task while remaining on schedule. These skills have been obtained through 3+ years within the hospitality industry. My skills have been refined through my experience both in my undergraduate BSc and in the workforce

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# January 2022 - present

**Position:** Customer Service Representative (Remote)

Location: Cork City, Ireland

- A part of a large, multi-departmental, international company, Capita Customer Solutions, that
  provides customer care for many major private and public companies such as Vodafone and
  Irish Water.
- Responsible for handling customers sensitive information, including financial information, and strictly adhering to GDPR for Irish Water customers
- Provide friendly and helpful customer service and maintaining composure, regardless of the customers query or attitude
- Efficiently navigating and learning different internal systems

### March 2019 - September 2019

**Position:** Administrative Assistance

Location: Oranmore, Co. Galway

- Day to day running of the largest European Innovation Partnership (EIP) in Europe, the Hen Harrier Project
- Part of a team responsible for the delivery of a conservation programme to hundreds of farmers across Ireland
- Experienced using Microsoft products such as Office and Sharepoint
- Handling and management of large stores of EIP user information and GDPR sensitive data
- Experienced working with customers and providing a high level of customer service

June 2020 – January 2022

**Position:** Caregiver

Location: Galway

• Patience and understanding required for caring for a toddler

• Creative thinking and problem solving to help communicate and teach

• Responsible for the safety and wellbeing of a toddler

## March 2015 – August 2017

Position: Duty Manager

Location: Castletownbere, Co. Cork

 Responsible for the day to day running of the welcome centre and café for Ireland's largest Buddhist Meditation site, Dzogchen Beara Buddhist Meditation Centre and Café including

managing money, balancing the books,

• Providing a high standard of customer service to all visitors to the centre

• Experienced dealing with non-English speakers due to the many international visitors

 Due to the popularity and size of the centre, experienced in managing large workloads and dealing with many customers at once

# November 2017 - August 2018

Position: Kitchen Porter

Location: Cork City

• Cleaning and maintenance of kitchen areas in Tequila Jack's Bar and Restaurant

Emphasis on efficiency, coordination and organisation

• Managing and keeping records of stock and deliveries

• Working effectively under the pressure of a busy kitchen

## **EDUCATION**

2016 – 2020: University College Cork, BSc Government (Public Finance, Spanish, Sociology, Public

Administration)

Final Grade: 2.1 Second Class First Honours

2018 - 2019: Waseda University, Political Science (Japanese Economic History, Public Expenditure,

Western Philosophy)

Final Grade: 3.3 GPA

2010 - 2016: Beara Community School (Scoil Phobail Beara) (French, Irish, English, Maths, Biology,

Physics, DCG, History)

### **INTERESTS AND ACHIEVEMENTS**

Member of the UCC's Government and Politics Society

- Member of social justice group "Life Leeches Trafficking Changes Lives". Report present to the House of the Oireachtas, 2014
- Accepted into Waseda University, Tokyo, as part of a UCC exchange programme
- Completed Munster Programming Training in UCC, 2014
- HTML proficient
- Completed BIM Nautical Engineering course, 2014
- Qualified in CPR, 2014
- Member of the Mardyke Arena Sports Centre
- Studying Spanish
- Video editing and media creation
- Photoshop and video editing proficient